Guide to the Severo Perez Papers
The Wittliff Collections
- Plays, 1980-1997, undated
  - Soldierboy, 1980-1987
    - Publicity
      - "The Real War 1939-1945" Atlantic Monthly article, plus photocopy (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Flyers (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Programs and newsletters (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Synopsis of the play (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Handbill signed by cast (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Speak Only of Cats, 1997
    - Draft – Speak Only of Cats (working title), March 6, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Draft – Speak Only of Cats, June 5, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Books, 2009-2010, undated
  - The Challengers Aero Club, 2009-2010
    - First draft version registered with WGA (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Draft, January 2, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - First Draft, March 31, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 3-5)
    - First Draft, May 8, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Draft, July 20, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Draft, July 23, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Draft of various chapters, 2009-2010 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Draft, February 19, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Draft, undated (Box 41, Folder 2-5, Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    - Draft (Box 42, Folder 3-4)
    - Multiple drafts, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Second Draft (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
    - Partial draft, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Chapter outline/timeline (Box 43, Folder 4)
- The National Endowment for the Humanities, 1990
  - "Polynesians: Voyagers of Rediscovery", September 1990 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - "Citizen Stalin" (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - "The Restless Conscience", 1990 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - "Roman City" (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - "The Glory and the Power", September 12, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - "Five Suns: Origin Myths of Central Mexico", September 4, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - "The Creative Faculty", September 1990 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - "Trinidad's Calypso – Social, Cultural, Political Content" (Box 44, Folder 8)